https://abendgallery.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?  We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, credit cart or bank account information, e-mail address, mailing address, or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.   What do we use your information for?  Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests) To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site featureTo market our products or process sales To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.   Do we use cookies?  Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We use cookies from third-party partners such as Google and Facebook for marketing purposes. These Cookies allow us to display promotional material to you on other sites you visit across the Internet. We may also share information about your behavior on the Site with third parties (including operators of third-party websites and/or social networking sites) in order to show you targeted advertisements and other content that has been customized for you. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
“Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you--for example: FedEx and other shipping providers, Google Analytics third-party partners such as Google and Facebook--so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.  BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING  As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work. You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:  - Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads  - Google: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous  - Bing: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.   California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.   Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we will not knowingly or intentionally collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  Online Privacy Policy Only  This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.YOUR RIGHTS  If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.  Your Consent  By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.   Last Update  This policy was last modified on November 8, 2020   Contacting Us  If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  1261 Delaware St, Suite 2 Denver, CO 80204 USA  info[at]abendgallery.com 303-355-0950
Purchase
Make an Offer
Inquire
Add To Cart
Continue Shopping
View Cart
Make an Offer
We are most likely to accept offers of 10% or less off the list price.
Offer (fixed or percent off)
